ivipid.com 2018-02-17

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Ivipid.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (hereinafter referred to as "a User") of the http://ivipid.com website (hereinafter referred to as "Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ivipid.com

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from a User in a variety of ways including but not limited to occasions when User visits our Site, registers on the Site, places an order, fills out a form, responds to surveys, as well as it concerns other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. As appropriate, a User may be asked for his name or email address. A User may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from a User only if he voluntarily submits such information to us. A User can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent him from engaging in certain Site related activities. We do not collect information about the specifics of who a User is unless he specifically provides it to us.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include browser name, type of computer device and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider as well as other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places “cookies” on a his device’s hard drive in order to keep records and sometimes to track information about a User. A User may choose to set his web browser to refuse “cookies” or to alert him when “cookies” are being sent. If it happens so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

Ivipid.com may collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes:

  1. To run and operate our Site
  2. To improve customer service 

Information you provide us with helps to respond to your requests to support service more efficiently.

  3. To personalize user experience 

We may use information to generally understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided by our Site.

  4. To improve our Site 

We may use feedback you provide us with to improve our products and services.

  5. To process payments 

We may use the information a User provides about himself when placing an order only in order to execute this order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

  6. To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site activity 

To send User information he has agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to him.

  7. To manage product reviews and ratings 

We may use third party service providers to help us manage product reviews and ratings submitted by users.

  8. To send periodic emails 

We may use the email address to send User information and updates regarding his order. It may also be used to respond to User’s inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect User’s personal information, username, password, transactions information and data stored on our Site against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. Security of your personal identification information is of utmost concern to us. User’s ivipid videos and other content are limited-access where access is gained through an obscured URL system. This obscured URL makes it difficult if not impossible for a third party to guess the URL address of User’s video or content without an invitation from this User including the relevant URL. However, because videos and content are not password-protected, a possibility exists that an unauthorized third party could discover User’s videos and/or content.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent User’s personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information irrelevant to any personal identification information of Site’s visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes mentioned above. We may use third party service providers to help us to operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share User’s information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that a User has given us his permission.

## Accessing Web Account Information

A User must update his personal identification information promptly after it changes. A User may change this information by sending us an e-mail. A User may ask to have the information in his account to be deleted or removed at any time. We will use reasonable efforts to delete User’s information however, because we and our web hosting company have backup systems and keep track of past transactions and/or activities, it may be impossible to completely delete User’s information.

## Electronic newsletters

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, he will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If a User does not want these mailings, he can send us a request to unsubscribe him. We may use third party service providers to help us to operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share User’s information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that he has given us his permission.

## Third party websites

A User may find advertising or other content on our Site that lead to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control any content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by such sites. In addition, these sites or services including their content and links may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Ivipid.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do so, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

You further acknowledge and agree that you are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13 years old, you do not have permission to access this site.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: support@ivipid.com

This document was last updated on March 14, 2017
